OLAEWE SAMUEL SHINA

No 10, Engr. Oyekan Crescent, Igbo-asio Igboora, Oyo State <u>Samuelshina2016@gmail.com</u> 08159488713, 08021323727

CARREER OBJECTIVES

A team player, with a commitment to customer's service, who possesses a long track record of working in various administrative roles.

Coupled with good PC skills and abilities to communicate confidently at all levels.

Apart from being immediately available, I have a strong background in general administration along with experience of working with a customer focused company like yours.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 24th April, 1990

Marital Status: Married

Sex: Male

State of Origin: Oyo

Local Govt. Area: Ibarapa Central

Nationality: Nigeria

Language Spoken: English and Yoruba

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATION

2016 Oyo State College of Agriculture and Technology, Igboora. Oyo

State

HND Home and Rural Economics

2007 Ayelogun Grammar School, Idere. Oyo State.

Senior Certificate (S.S.C.E.)

2000 Islamic Mission School II, Idere. Oyo State.

First School Leaving Certificate

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2018-2019: **Greatwood Hotel, Owerri. Imo State**

Administrative Officer

2017-2018: Starnet Technology, Owerri Imo State

National Youth Service Corps. Sales Representative

2013-2014: Celplast Industries Limited, Shagamu. Ogun State

Quality and Control Officer

SKILLS/ABILITIES

Ability to adapt to changes and work in dynamic environment.

- Hardworking, dutiful and reliable.
- Time conscious approach to teamwork matched with self-sacrificing personal traits.
- Ability to work under pressure
- Excellent communication and listening skills
- Good knowledge and experience of Microsoft office packages

REFEREES:

Mr. Akintola Akintunde

Department of engineering. Oyo State college of Agriculture and Technology

Igboora. Oyo State

08060673455

Mrs. Oni Oluwatoyin

Oyo State College of Agriculture and Technology

Igboora, Oyo state.

08133065959

Mr. Dele Nihinlola

World Health Organization. Abuja

08033833939